<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description_format">%1$s, %2$s</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_subtitle_description_format">%1$s, %2$s, %3$s</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_body_1_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_body_2_material">sans-serif-medium</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_button_material">sans-serif-medium</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_caption_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_1_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_2_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_3_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_4_material">sans-serif-light</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_headline_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_menu_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_subhead_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_title_material">sans-serif-medium</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="accelerator">Neural Accelerator</string>
    <string name="accelerator_description_message">"The most efficient reading or training practice is achieved when a body is relaxed and a brain is active. A relaxed state of alertness is reached, and thus the text is understood and digested. 

One has to squint his eyes and try to give once over the text to be read as much as possible. 

You can use the \"tangerine technique\" to quickly and easily establish a perfect state of relaxed alertness. This simple method automatically directs your attention in the right direction and improves reading quality instantly. 

Classes show that both reading and memory require attention. 

A unit of attention focusing is of vital importance. For instance, when driving a car the best unit of attention is the road spreading out in front of you but not a bonnet or a bumper. The space at the back and on top of the head is ideal place to establishing point of attention. 

The \"tangerine technique\" helps to identify an ideal area of attention and to control it. The technique helps also to enter into a desirable for reading relaxed and alert state of body and mind. The below instructions are to be followed: 

Imagine a tangerine. Now drop it to other hand and catch it. Sense its weight, color, skin and smell. Lob it from hand to hand. 

Now catch the tangerine with your dominant hand and position it on the top of your head. Touch that area gently. Imagine the tangerine underlying there; meanwhile you bring hand down and relax your shoulders. You may pretend this is a magical tangerine and it will always stay where you place it. 

Close your eyes slowly and keep the on your head. Notice the changes in your physical and mental state as you do this. You will feel relaxed and alert. With your eyes closed, imagine your field of vision viewable. 

Control the relaxed feeling of alertness after you open your eyes and start reading. 

By playing around with this technique you will absorb reading material easier and will do this very fast. Your will develop ability to concentrate on the information and reading will become more relaxing. 

Firstly, you will consciously place the tangerine onto your head. Then it will become an automatic process and whenever you take reading material in hand, one unit of attention will occupy its place. 

This kind of a state of physical relax and mental alert is useful also for other areas of activity. It has been studied in detail as the state when a person is most productive. This state is similar to thoughtfulness, meditation when a person is all about just the present moment. 

However, this state of relaxation isn’t like drowsiness. You rather focus the brain on anything with a sense of inner quietness. You have access to entire internal natural resources. 

More about the tangerine technique 

It is difficult for many people to reach the ideal reading state, especially when at work. While reading in the office a phone rings permanently, you have to hurry not to be late and thoughts are jammed in your head of the enterprise products or of the car repair. What will be the attention concentrated on if the brain has been turned into a swamp? Onto everything by little. It will be become virtually impossible to read. 

Ideal reading state is fundamentally different. It is the state of a flow when you are completely wrapped up into the material spread out in front. This is the spot where the \"tangerine technique\" comes into play. 

Highly skilled readers have their point of attention clearly identified; it’s located a bit to the rear and upper the top of the head. 

Many people noticed a number of benefits gained after using the “tangerine technique\". To start with, they were fast and easy to enter into the state of relaxed alertness. In addition they calm down the brain and focus automatically on the desired object. The result is instant improvement of skills. 

The “tangerine technique\" has been appearing in various types throughout the entire mankind history. Each of them makes you concentrate attention on the spot just above and behind your head. 

Play around with this technique. If the tangerine image doesn't help try to focus on the desired spot another way. Imagine wearing a sombrero and a bird just sat down on it. Sense the hat but concentrate your attention on the bird. 

Here’s another way. Imagine yourself being outside the body and looking at the top of your head while reading. At that time take note of your feelings changing. 

Curious thing happens when you open your eyes while having focused attention with one of the techniques. All of a sudden the material read becomes more controllable. Viewing field gets broader. In this kind of a state you are able to acquire much more information visually. 

The goal is to achieve such a state of the brain. You are trying to keep the tangerine throughout the entire reading. Establishing a fixed point of attention is like placing a keystone on the top of an archway. One stone at the top maintains all the others. 

Likewise, one point of attention focused concentrates and directs any others to a purpose of reading. Having established it once you don’t have to worry any longer. When you walk through the door you don’t need to take it away with you. Just move forward and start reading and your brain will take care of everything else. 

Take some minutes to figure out how you can use the knowledge gained from this chapter: 
The two components of training are setting a goal and transition into the ideal state with a fixed point of attention being on the top of your head. 
Goal-oriented reading means efficient reading. 
The “tangerine technique\" is one of the most powerful methods to maintain attention that automatically puts your brain in the ideal state. 

Once again note the changes in physical state happening in the meantime. While reading you feel more relaxed, concentrated, attentive and fully absorbed by reading. Now you are prepared to study. 

If you master the tangerine technique and get rid of uttering the speed boundaries will vanish. 

In order to get qualitative results self-discipline, regularity of classes and careful execution of all exercises are required. You should practice 2 times a day, one hour in the morning and one hour in the evening. 

Good luck in speed reading and success at everything."</string>
    <string name="accelerator_description_title">The ways how to practice and read a text better</string>
    <string name="accelerator_result_duration_title">Duration</string>
    <string name="accelerator_result_min">%1$s min</string>
    <string name="accelerator_result_sec">%1$s sec</string>
    <string name="accelerator_settings_column_count_default_value">1</string>
    <string name="accelerator_settings_column_count_key">accelerator_column_count</string>
    <string name="accelerator_settings_column_count_summary">Column count</string>
    <string name="accelerator_settings_column_count_title">Column count</string>
    <string name="accelerator_settings_duration_default_value">60000</string>
    <string name="accelerator_settings_duration_key">accelerator_duration</string>
    <string name="accelerator_settings_duration_summary">Duration of the training</string>
    <string name="accelerator_settings_duration_title">Duration</string>
    <string name="accelerator_speed">Speed %1$d</string>
    <string name="accelerator_time">Time %1$s</string>
    <string name="advices">Advice</string>
    <string name="all_books">All books</string>
    <string name="app_name">Speed Reading</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="application_url">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.speedreading.alexander.speedreading</string>
    <string name="banner_advertisement_id">ca-app-pub-1214906094509332/9299425407</string>
    <string name="base_course_name">Basic course</string>
    <string name="base_course_short_name">Base</string>
    <string name="base_profile">Base</string>
    <string name="begin">Begin</string>
    <string name="book">Our book</string>
    <string name="book_detail_author">Author</string>
    <string name="book_detail_file_path">The path to the file</string>
    <string name="book_detail_language">Language</string>
    <string name="book_detail_title">Title</string>
    <string name="bottom_menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="bottom_menu_materials">Material</string>
    <string name="bottom_menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="bottom_menu_reading">Reading</string>
    <string name="bottom_menu_training">Training</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_behavior">android.support.design.widget.BottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern">%1$d / %2$d</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">%1$s is having trouble with Google Play services. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="concentration">Сoncentration</string>
    <string name="concentration_complexity_auto">Automatic</string>
    <string name="concentration_complexity_self">Personal</string>
    <string name="concentration_complexity_title">Choose type of training</string>
    <string name="concentration_description_text">This simulator will help develop the ability to concentrate and improve attention. Exercises will help to perceive any information in a shorter period. A very useful skill at speed reading will allow you to keep the focus on the necessary tasks. Very well extends the field of view. It is very useful for children. Concentrate on the flying circles of blue, and after stopping, try to guess all previously colored balls.</string>
    <string name="count">Amount</string>
    <string name="course_max_points">Congratulations! The maximum rank</string>
    <string name="course_need_points">%1$d points left to the rank of %2$s</string>
    <string name="course_points_add_info">*To update the rank you must complete the course</string>
    <string name="courses">Courses</string>
    <string name="creating">In developing</string>
    <string name="cup_timer_settings_duration_default_value">300000</string>
    <string name="cup_timer_settings_duration_key">cup_timer_duration</string>
    <string name="cup_timer_settings_type_default_value">1</string>
    <string name="cup_timer_settings_type_key">cup_timer_type</string>
    <string name="cup_timer_settings_type_summary">Type of training</string>
    <string name="cup_timer_settings_type_title">Type</string>
    <string name="cuptimer">Focusing of attention</string>
    <string name="cuptimer_description_text">"Home Your task is to concentrate as much as possible on the image of green color.         

It is necessary to force myself to think only about the profile that is highlighted by this color.         

 Looking at the picture, we can see a vase or two human profiles.         

If thoughts are distracted by other tasks, we must force ourselves to concentrate on the image of green color.         

This is a very useful exercise for mastering the technique of fast reading.         

The simulator is simple and at the same time very effective, it helps to solve several problems at once: learn to concentrate and, looking at the text, do not pronounce the words.         

To concentrate not only external peace, but also inner peace is needed.         

Before getting started, relax and gather. Discard all thoughts relating to other things.         

Expand your eyes and try to see 3 pictures, pay attention only to the image in the center.         

The principle of stereo is borrowed from stereo pictures. Relax your eyes and try to see 3 pictures.         

All attention only to the image in the center. It has a very beneficial effect on our eyes.         

The eyes are focused on the picture at the time of the greatest relaxation of the muscles. This helps relieve tension and fatigue from the eyes.         

Regular examination helps maintain eye freshness and visual acuity. Exercise helps to expand the field of vision, dilute the eye axes and learn to concentrate on the text, covering large fragments.         

Stereo images are often used by ophthalmologists to treat binocular disorders. They are a useful tool for developing two eyes."</string>
    <string name="cuptimer_info">Focus on green</string>
    <string name="current_level">Level %1$d</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">600224958351-6o4bjcb7b9eftdrcvqrmpj1pgk47f090.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="description_do_not_show_it_again">"Don't show it again"</string>
    <string name="description_start">Start</string>
    <string name="dialog_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="dialog_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="dialog_help">Help</string>
    <string name="dialog_restart">Restart</string>
    <string name="dialog_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="even_numbers">Even numbers</string>
    <string name="even_numbers_best_score">Best %1$d</string>
    <string name="even_numbers_description_message">"Your task is to quickly find and press on 6 even numbers each time the table shows. 

This exercise improves your attention focusing and accuracy of image perception. 

Stay relaxed and choose a convenient option whether to navigate through the columns or rows."</string>
    <string name="even_numbers_description_title">Even numbers</string>
    <string name="even_numbers_result_best_score">Best</string>
    <string name="even_numbers_result_new_best">New best</string>
    <string name="even_numbers_result_score">Score</string>
    <string name="even_numbers_score">Score %1$d</string>
    <string name="file_explorer_book_adding">The book is adding</string>
    <string name="file_explorer_book_adding_failed">Book adding error</string>
    <string name="file_explorer_book_adding_success">The book was added to the library</string>
    <string name="file_explorer_book_already_exist">The book is already in the library</string>
    <string name="file_explorer_file_type">File type %1$s</string>
    <string name="file_explorer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="firebase_database_url">https://speedreading-ebcaa.firebaseio.com</string>
    <string name="flash_words">Flash words</string>
    <string name="flash_words_level">Level %1$d</string>
    <string name="flash_words_settings_duration_default_value">60000</string>
    <string name="flash_words_settings_duration_key">flash_words_duration</string>
    <string name="flash_words_settings_duration_summary">Duration of the training</string>
    <string name="flash_words_settings_duration_title">Duration</string>
    <string name="forever_premium">Buy forever for %1$s</string>
    <string name="gcm_defaultSenderId">600224958351</string>
    <string name="getting_rid_of_pronouncing">Getting rid of pronouncing</string>
    <string name="google_api_key">AIzaSyArrfAd5gGosgHG6tuU1pyT2-M8-tLV5Cg</string>
    <string name="google_app_id">1:600224958351:android:eff310eb4e59244a</string>
    <string name="google_crash_reporting_api_key">AIzaSyArrfAd5gGosgHG6tuU1pyT2-M8-tLV5Cg</string>
    <string name="google_storage_bucket">speedreading-ebcaa.appspot.com</string>
    <string name="green_dot">Green Dot</string>
    <string name="green_dot_description_message_1">"This exercise greatly contributes to the expansion of the field of vision. 

Contemplation of the green point allows you to distinguish the outlines, outlines of words surrounding the green point, phrases, sentences and gradually you can see all the large and large fragments of the text. 

Exercise should be performed for 3 months daily without interruption."</string>
    <string name="green_dot_description_message_2">"To do the exercises, you need to sit up straight and at all times to relax, have a steady and calm breathing. 

The screen should be at a distance - 30-35 cm from the eyes, as in reading the book. 

Before performing gymnastics for the eyes: the head is still. Look down, up, left, right, away, near. 

You need to focus on the green spot for 10 minutes: (15, 20, 30, 60, not more than 120 minutes). The text during the contemplation of the green dot is not read. ONLY A GREEN POINT. 

Reading is always about eye movement."</string>
    <string name="green_dot_description_message_3">"When contemplating a green point, you go through several stages. As the concentration increases, it is easier to keep attention on the point. But eventually you can relax and the green dot can begin to swim in different directions: left-right, up-down, approaching you and moving away from you. 

It is important that the eyes without any effort stopped on it, and all extraneous thoughts disappeared. Thanks to this vision, the green dot becomes REPORTING, BRIGHT. The clarity of consciousness is reached, which is the main goal of the exercises. 

When it starts to work out (it takes 1-2 weeks), the task is to gradually increase the perception. page horizontally. Then you should see 2-3 lines of text below and above the green point - do not read the text, but FEEL its presence."</string>
    <string name="green_dot_description_message_4">"When contemplating a green point, you learn not to be distracted by extraneous thoughts, which leads to something that would not catch up, just a few moments, but that's enough."</string>
    <string name="green_dot_description_title">Green dot</string>
    <string name="green_dot_description_title_2">Training Mode</string>
    <string name="green_dot_description_title_3">Recommendations</string>
    <string name="green_dot_description_title_4">Purpose</string>
    <string name="green_dot_pass_course_result_duration">Duration %1$s</string>
    <string name="green_dot_result_duration_title">Duration</string>
    <string name="green_dot_settings_duration_default_value">600000</string>
    <string name="green_dot_settings_duration_key">green_dot_duration</string>
    <string name="green_dot_settings_duration_summary">Duration of the training</string>
    <string name="green_dot_settings_duration_title">Duration</string>
    <string name="green_dot_text">"I am absolutely calm. I am absolutely calm. Speed reading gives me joy, feeling of lightness. Inspiration. I do not get tired, and I feel better every day. Learning to read is easy for me. By training, I remain free, fresh. Not I am trying to imagine what is described as vividly as possible. I read any text only once, however difficult the text is. I always use the first rule of speed reading - read without regressions. My eyes are moving easily and smoothly only forward. I can read this way. I will always read this way. I read fast. I always remember the seven blocks of the integral reading algorithm. I can see the visual image of the algorithm distinctly and clearly. When reading a text, I easily distribute its contents between the algorithm blocks. All unnecessary things are omitted. The new reading program is acting on its own, out of habit. I will always read this way. I read fast. I always see the main meaning of the text – its dominant. I can see it clearly. It pops up like on a screen, in relief, brightly, in contrast. I can always write it in my own words, in the language of my own thoughts. I read fast. I have no articulation. I remember the rhythm of its supression. It doesn't allow talking. I will always remember it. I read faster and faster. I feel that every day my eyesight becomes sharper, more focused, strong. My field of vision is ever expanding. Every day I can see the whole page better, I can see the whole text at once, clearly, distinctly. My view is free, calm, clear. Eyes are moving easily and freely along the text only vertically, from top to bottom, on the page center. I can read in fifteen seconds, in seven seconds, in one second. I can see the text like on the screen. I can clearly see the whole page at once. I an trying to imagine what is described as vividly as possible. I feel strong, young, healthy. My nervous system, my whole body is full of energy, tranquility, stamina, strength. My sleep is deep and sound. I read surprisingly fast. I am always attentive, concentrated. Foreign thoughts do not bother me. I dominate my attention. I train my attention all the time. My memory is perfect. My memory improves every day. Important information is memorized on its own, without any efforts, and displayed like on the screen – completely and accurately. I read fast. I enjoy the speed reading method. I read freely, easily, with tranquility. I am absolutely calm. I am absolutely calm. Fast reading gives me joy, feeling of lightness, inspiration. I do not get tired, and I feel better every day. I read fast. I coded new programs and reading codes in my brain, in my mind. I will always read fast."</string>
    <string name="half_year_premium">6 months</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="interstitial_advertisement_id">ca-app-pub-1214906094509332/5949653003</string>
    <string name="interstitial_next_training">Next training</string>
    <string name="interstitial_restart">Course restart</string>
    <string name="interstitial_restart_button">Restart</string>
    <string name="interstitial_restart_description">Are you sure you want to restart the course?</string>
    <string name="interstitial_start">Start</string>
    <string name="level">Level</string>
    <string name="library">Library</string>
    <string name="library_book_deleting">Book is deleting</string>
    <string name="library_book_progress">Progress %1$d%%</string>
    <string name="library_book_remove_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="library_book_remove_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="library_book_remove_message">Do you want to delete this book from your library?</string>
    <string name="library_data_loading">Data are loading</string>
    <string name="library_format_dialog_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="library_format_dialog_do_not_show_again">Do not show again</string>
    <string name="library_format_dialog_message">"This app supports the following book formats: 
- fb2 (fb2.zip) 
- epub 
- txt"</string>
    <string name="library_format_dialog_title">Supported formats</string>
    <string name="library_is_empty">Library is empty</string>
    <string name="library_permission_denied">Memory access permission denied</string>
    <string name="library_permission_set">Set</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight">Line of sight</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_description_message">"Your task is to determine whether there is a discrepancy between the letters at the edges of the table. If there is a mismatch, click the Error button. 

Focus your view in the center of the screen and try to see the whole table. The main task is to focus on the screen and memorize all the inconsistencies, fixing them with the button.If letters are displayed too quickly you may press the \"Error\" button with some delay, but try to remember the existence of all discrepancies and make sure you press the \"Error\" button for each discrepancy. 

This is a very useful exercise that not only helps you expand your peripheral vision, but also makes you concentrate within a limited show time, which is crucial, among other things, for speed reading."</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_description_title">Line of sight</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_mistake">Mistake</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_pass_course_result_accuracy">Accuracy %1$s</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_pass_course_result_found_mistakes">Found mistakes %1$d</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_pass_course_result_mistakes">Mistakes %1$d</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_result_found_mistakes">You found</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_result_found_mistakes_accuracy">Accuracy</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_result_mistakes">Mistakes</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_settings_board_size_summary">Board size</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_settings_board_size_title">Board size</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_settings_field_type_preference_default_value">0</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_settings_field_type_preference_key">line_of_sight_field_type</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_settings_field_type_summary">Field type</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_settings_field_type_title">Field type</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_settings_row_count_preference_default_value">5</string>
    <string name="line_of_sight_settings_row_count_preference_key">line_of_sight_row_count</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description_message_1">"Quality results require self-discipline, regular and careful practicing in all exercises. Exercise twice a day for two hours, an hour in the morning and an hour in the evening. You can exercise more but try to avoid fatigue. Exercises are simple but require careful and daily performance, and now it's the most ideal time to successfully start and learn something new. We hope that speed reading will become your lifestyle. If you are ready to perform exercises aimed at developing the speed of reading, then we wish you good luck and you will certainly succeed. Take a minute to compile a list of the most commonly used sources for reading in your mind. Among them might be: Websites and electronic documents Entertaining and scientific journals Newspapers Letters and e-mails Notes Instructions or manuals Educational materials Reports Trade offers Professional documents Scientific literature Novels, poetry and stories Quickly answer the following questions in your mind: How well do you perceive the material read? How well do you remember the material you read? What are your strengths? What is the main feature that you would like to change in yourself when reading?"</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description_message_2_part_1">1 Read without regressions. 2 Read according to the integral reading algorithm. 3 Always highlight the dominant (the main meaning of the text). 4 Read without articulation. 5 Read with the vertical movement of the eyes. 6 Constantly develop your attention and memory. 7 Perform a daily compulsory task: read 100-200 pages of any book. These can be newspapers, magazines, the Internet, scientific and technical or popular science literature. You will learn all these rules through our exercises.</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description_message_2_part_2">Reading is the most effective when the body is in a relaxed state, and the brain is active. When a state of relaxed vigilance is reached, the text is better perceived and digested. In order to quickly and effortlessly achieve the state of perfect relaxed vigilance, you can use the tangerine technique. This simple method automatically directs your attention in the right way and instantly improves quality of reading. Practice shows that both reading and memory require attention. On the conscious level in one session you can perceive up to seven, plus or minus two, bits of information. Studies also show that focusing one unit of attention on the initial topic contributes to the effective use of the remaining units when reading. The subject of attention focusing is essential. For example, while driving, the best subject of attention is the road ahead, not the hood or bumper. For effective reading, the ideal subject for focusing is the space behind and above the top back part of your head. The tangerine technique helps determine and control the ideal area of attention. The technique also helps enter into the desired relaxed, watchful state of the body and mind. It is necessary to follow the following instructions: Imagine a tangerine. Feel its weight, color, peel and smell. Now throw it into the other hand and catch it. Keep throwing the tangerine from hand to hand. Now catch the tangerine with your leading hand and put it onto the top of your head. Gently touch this place. Imagine the tangerine lying there; at the same time you lower your arms and relax your shoulders. You can imagine that this is a magical tangerine, and it will stay where you put it. Slowly close your eyes and hold the tangerine on your head. Pay attention to changes in the physical and mental state during this procedure. You will feel relaxed and aware. Keeping the eyes closed, imagine the visual field visible. Control the feeling of relaxed awareness after you open your eyes and start reading. By experimenting with this technique, you can absorb the text you read more easily and at a very high speed. You will develop the ability to concentrate on information, and reading will become more relaxing. At first, you will consciously put the tangerine on your head. Then it will happen automatically, and as soon as you pick up a text for reading, one unit of attention will instantly take its place. This state of physical relaxation and mental watchfulness is also useful for other areas of activity. It was studied in detail as a state where a person is most productive. This state is similar to reverie, meditation, when a person is only absorbed by the present moment. However, this state of relaxation is not like drowsiness. Rather, you focus your brain on something with a sense of inner tranquility. You have access to all internal natural resources. More about the tangerine technique Many people find it difficult to achieve an ideal state for reading, especially at work. When reading in the office, the phone is constantly ringing, you have to hurry up so as not to be late, and in your head a congestion of thoughts about the products of the enterprise or about repairing the car is formed. What will attention be directed to if the brain has turned into such a swamp? To everything by little. Reading will become almost impossible. The ideal state for reading is completely different. This is the state of flow when you are completely absorbed by the material lying in front of you. It is here that the tangerine technique comes into play. In highly educated readers, on the contrary, the point of attention is clearly defined; it is located just behind and above the top of the head. Many people have noticed several benefits obtained after using the tangerine technique. For a start, they learned to move into a state of relaxed vigilance quickly and easily. In addition, they soothe their brains and automatically focus their attention on the desired object. The result is instant improvement of skills. The tangerine technique was manifested in various forms throughout the history of mankind. Each of them makes you fix attention on the spot just above and behind the head. Experiment with this technique. If the image of the tangerine does not help, try to focus your attention on the right place in another way. Imagine wearing a sombrero, and a bird sat on it. Feel the hat, and concentrate on the bird. Another way. Imagine that while reading you are standing outside the body and looking at the top of your head. During this, pay attention to changing your sensations. A curious thing happens when you, having fixed your attention using one of these techniques, open your eyes. Unexpectedly, readable material becomes more manageable. The field of view is expanding. In this state, you are able to visually perceive much more information. Achieving such a state of the brain is the goal. You do not try to keep the tangerine throughout the whole reading. Establishing a fixed point of attention is similar to placing a key stone in the upper part of the archway. One stone on top holds all the rest. Similarly, one focused point of attention collects and directs all others to the reading task. Having installed it once, you can stop worrying. When you pass through the door, you do not need to take it with you. Just move on and start reading - your brain will take care of everything else. Take a few minutes to determine how you can use the knowledge gained in this chapter: * The two components of preparation are the goal setting and the transition to the ideal state with a fixed point of attention on the top of your head. * To read purposefully means to read effectively. * Tangerine technique is one of the most effective ways to fix attention, which automatically translates your brain into the ideal state. Once again, notice the changes that occur during this change in the physical state. When reading, you feel more relaxed, concentrated, attentive and completely absorbed in the book. Now you are ready to learn. The next step is ..</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description_message_4">In the morning: 30 minutes of exercises 30-40 minutes of reading (15-20 minutes for each mode) In the evening: 30 minutes of exercises 30-40 minutes of reading (15-20 minutes for each mode) Later we will add a variety of high-performance simulators, thanks to which you can further increase your memory and speed reading capabilities.</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description_message_5" formatted="false">You may not believe it, but people who have this ability can read 100-200 pages on the way to work, in the metro or other public transport. By developing the skill of speed reading, you save time and can learn more useful material. Many students managed to reach the speed of 4 thousand words per minute with 70% understanding. In order to reach the speed of 1-2 thousand words per minute, people with different levels of training require an average of 2 hours of exercise per day. You can devote 60 minutes a day depending on how fast you want to achieve the result! Our application contains unique methods that implement global experience helping you achieve the desired speed of reading without taking expensive courses. Speed reading does not mean reading faster. First of all, it means development of memory, attention and expanding the field of vision. It is a basis for further development in various intellectual areas: learning foreign languages, comprehensive preparation for entrance examination, mastering new profession. Training in the speed reading technique you learn a lot of useful skills and traits that you might not have before, such as self-discipline, diligence, attentiveness, stamina, creative thinking, etc. Consistency, steadiness and self-discipline of training are the key to success. Our brain is a muscle that needs to be fed and trained. Thus you can achieve any results that you can only dream of. When working with our program, a person undergoes positive changes: one comes to know oneself, opens a new world, gains new opportunities. Such self-discovery has an incredible effect. One becomes more self-confident. The world around them gets better. One starts thinking differently, does more, becomes more dynamic and full of energy. Effective and creative thinking, right decision taking are those advantages that users of our application get. Speed reading is a very useful skill. It helps a person perceive the text and to read it within the shortest time. It saves time. How to increase speed of text perception, and do you need to read the text several times? Let’s find out. In general, no book, article, or other form of text will be precisely remembered at the first time. Therefore the first reading of any text can only result in some impression of the text. But this impression is based on emotions, which a person remembers. That’s why it is easy to remember whether a movie was interesting or not. But it often happens that a person cannot remember the protagonist’s name. What does it mean? We are not able to understand the information read at the first time. More than a million books are issued every year, as well as many other unique tests, articles, etc. It’s just important to take and use what you need. But how can one read such a huge amount of information that exists in the world? The answer is simple: learn speed reading. It’s an incredible useful skill that can help a person become more educated in a couple of months. Everyone can do this. If you set the goal, speed reading allows reading five books per day. And even more. Some people who successfully mastered speed reading can read one page in five seconds and retell its contents. You can also achieve such results. Reading is a process consisting of four steps: perception, understanding, remembering, reproduction. It is not enough to read a text, you need to understand what is written and, if possible, to give a short summary. Time spent on reading is reduced, which is very important for busy people. You will have more time that can be spent with your beloved ones. You will learn to process texts quickly, to find the most important information at once, to develop memory, attention and vocabulary. You will open a new world of reading, since you can read any literature from professional one to fiction. If you use books for studying, it will be more effective, and no book will be complicated for you. The new skill will increase your self-esteem and self-confidence. The advantages are evident: by reading more than 1 book per month you outrun 90% of your rivals, by reading more than 4 books you outrun 99% of them. Why do you need speed reading? Search for a new job. With speed reading, you are faster and better than your competitors. In the economic crisis, unemployment, uncertainty, the one who has information owns the world. Speed and memory. The more you know, the better you learn, the better you perform, the easier you work. Earn money. You will always be on time, find new clients, opportunities. You will be noticed, promoted. What will you learn? You will read much faster. You will be able to estimate information on time and not after reading it, to omit the unnecessary one and to immediately determine the one you need. Learn not to waste time on empty texts. You will exceed your competitors, inspire respect of your partners, superiors, and inferiors! You will be able to get ready for exams quickly, remember information easily, be always on time, find spare time for friends, family, hobby, more reading, impress with your knowledge. You life will take a turn for the better. You will succeed. The key to success is consistency, steadiness and self-discipline of training. Speed reading as the way of life.</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description_title_1">How to deal with our program</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description_title_2">Seven basic rules for fast reading</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description_title_4">Total</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description_title_5">Why do you need speed reading?</string>
    <string name="math_complexity_choose">Choose a difficulty level:</string>
    <string name="math_complexity_easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="math_complexity_hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="math_complexity_mixed">Mixed</string>
    <string name="math_complexity_normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="math_correct_answer">Correct answer: %1$d</string>
    <string name="math_description_text">Correctly answer the mathematical examples. Consider the time limit, which you can change in the settings of the simulator. Mathematics helps to train areas of the brain that are also used for speed reading.</string>
    <string name="math_settings_duration_default_value">10000</string>
    <string name="math_settings_duration_key">math_duration</string>
    <string name="mathematics">Mathematics</string>
    <string name="mixed_up_letters">Mixed up letters</string>
    <string name="month_premium">1 month</string>
    <string name="more">Read more</string>
    <string name="more_speed_ads_description">Increase the maximum reading speed to 3000 characters per minute</string>
    <string name="more_speed_ads_title">At high speed</string>
    <string name="more_training_ads_description">"Open access to the 'Focusing' and 'Memorize words' trainers"</string>
    <string name="more_training_ads_title">Full access to exercises</string>
    <string name="motivators">Motivators</string>
    <string name="motivators_title">You will succeed!</string>
    <string name="need_points">another %1$d points</string>
    <string name="new_books">Recently Added</string>
    <string name="no_ads_description">Get even more comfort without being distracted by the ad blocks in the app</string>
    <string name="no_ads_title">No ads</string>
    <string name="notification_first_type">Concentrate on green objects</string>
    <string name="notification_second_type">Turn the screen horizontally and focus on the center of the image</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="notifications_settings_notify_key">notifications_notify</string>
    <string name="notifications_settings_notify_time_key">notifications_notify_time</string>
    <string name="notifications_settings_set_time_title">Set time</string>
    <string name="notifications_settings_title">Daily notifications</string>
    <string name="pass_course">Pass the course</string>
    <string name="pass_course_current_trainer">Current simulator</string>
    <string name="pass_course_next">Next</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating">Rating</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating_beginner">Beginner</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating_expert">Expert</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating_genius">Genius</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating_guru">Guru</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating_learner">Learner</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating_master">Master</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating_not_passed">Course not started</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating_professor">Professor</string>
    <string name="pass_course_rating_score">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="pass_course_reading_description">You should read book in two modes for 15 minutes</string>
    <string name="pass_course_result_t">Result</string>
    <string name="pass_course_score">Score</string>
    <string name="pass_course_trainers_left">Simulators left: %1$d</string>
    <string name="pass_course_training_number">Training %1$d</string>
    <string name="pass_descr">"Quality results require self-discipline, regular classes and careful execution of all exercises. You need to study 2 times a day - one hour in the morning and one hour in the evening. 

Regularity of classes is one of the key elements. 

After the exercises, you need to read within 15 (minutes) in the \"Fast\" mode and 15 minutes in the \"Sighting\" mode. The speed should be chosen 2 times higher than your own and increased step by step. At the first stage memorizing is not required. If you are willing to perform exercises aimed at advancing of your reading speed, we wish you good luck then and you will make it. 

Our program includes unique methods incorporated the global experience. After the course is fully completed, you will be able to increase your reading speed by 5-10 times."</string>
    <string name="pass_descr_close">Close</string>
    <string name="pass_descr_start">Start</string>
    <string name="pass_descr_title">How to study with the program \"Pass the course\"</string>
    <string name="password_toggle_content_description">Toggle password visibility</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye">M12,4.5C7,4.5 2.73,7.61 1,12c1.73,4.39 6,7.5 11,7.5s9.27,-3.11 11,-7.5c-1.73,-4.39 -6,-7.5 -11,-7.5zM12,17c-2.76,0 -5,-2.24 -5,-5s2.24,-5 5,-5 5,2.24 5,5 -2.24,5 -5,5zM12,9c-1.66,0 -3,1.34 -3,3s1.34,3 3,3 3,-1.34 3,-3 -1.34,-3 -3,-3z</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye_mask_strike_through">M2,4.27 L19.73,22 L22.27,19.46 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1 L23,1 L23,23 L1,23 L1,4.27 Z</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye_mask_visible">M2,4.27 L2,4.27 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1 L23,1 L23,23 L1,23 L1,4.27 Z</string>
    <string name="path_password_strike_through">M3.27,4.27 L19.74,20.74</string>
    <string name="pay_for">When paying for</string>
    <string name="per_month">/mo</string>
    <string name="points_left">Points left: %1$d</string>
    <string name="premium">Premium</string>
    <string name="premium_description">"Speed to 3000 
No ads"</string>
    <string name="prepare_title">Get ready</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy"><u>Privacy policy</u></string>
    <string name="project_id">speedreading-ebcaa</string>
    <string name="purchase">Purchase</string>
    <string name="purchase_error">Billing system error</string>
    <string name="purchase_success">You got premium access</string>
    <string name="random_trainer">Random Vocabulary trainer</string>
    <string name="rate_app_dialog_dont_show_again">No, thanks</string>
    <string name="rate_app_dialog_message">"Hi! If you like our application and you are interested in it's development, spend a minute of your time to leave your feedback."</string>
    <string name="rate_app_dialog_rate_now">Rate it now</string>
    <string name="rate_app_dialog_remind_me_later">Remind me later</string>
    <string name="rate_app_dialog_title">Rate application</string>
    <string name="reader_exit_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="reader_exit_dialog_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="reader_exit_dialog_message">Do you really want to exit?</string>
    <string name="reader_exit_dialog_title">Exit</string>
    <string name="reader_file_opening">Opening the file</string>
    <string name="reader_file_opening_error">Error opening the file</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_center_description">"Click on the central third of the screen to pause or to resume training 

Click twice on the central third of the screen to call a navigation menu"</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_default_reading_center_description">Click twice on the central third of the screen to call a navigation menu</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_default_reading_message">"This mode allows to read books providing the ability to turn pages independently. 

You need to try to read with defocused sight. Make it a routine to reach the maximum amount of text. 

It is not necessary to fully understand the read text in the early stages."</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_default_reading_title">Usual reading</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_do_not_show_again">Do not show again</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_fast_reading_message">"This mode allows to read books using the automatic page turning with the help of cursor highlighting the text. 

You need to try to read with defocused sight. Make it a routine to reach the maximum amount of text. 

It is not necessary to fully understand the read text in the early stages."</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_fast_reading_title">Speed reading</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_flash_reading_message">"This mode allows to read books using the automatic page turning without highlighting the single words. 

You need to try to read with defocused sight. Make it a routine to reach the maximum amount of text. 

It is not necessary to fully understand the read text in the early stages."</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_flash_reading_title">Sighting mode</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_next_page_description">Click on the right third of the screen to go to the next page</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_pencil_frame_description">Use navigation menu to change the number of highlighted lines.</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_pencil_frame_reading_message">"This mode allows to read books using the automatic page turning highlighting the separate parts of text. 

You need to try to read with defocused sight. Make it a routine to reach the maximum amount of text. 

It is not necessary to fully understand the read text in the early stages."</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_pencil_frame_reading_title">Pencil reading</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_pencil_frame_selected_line_minus_description">Click on minus to reduce the number of highlighted lines.</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_pencil_frame_selected_line_plus_description">Click on plus to increase the number of highlighted lines.</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_previous_page_description">Click on the left third of the screen to go to the previous page</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_speed_down_description">Click on the left third of the screen to reduce speed</string>
    <string name="reader_guide_dialog_speed_up_description">Click on the right third of the screen to increase speed</string>
    <string name="reader_navigation_page">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="reader_page">Page %1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="reader_pencil_frame_selected_line_count">Lines %1$d</string>
    <string name="reader_pencil_frame_selected_line_count_key">reader_selected_line_count</string>
    <string name="reader_purchase_premium_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="reader_purchase_premium_dialog_message">To use all opportunities you should buy premium access</string>
    <string name="reader_purchase_premium_dialog_purchase">Purchase</string>
    <string name="reader_purchase_premium_dialog_title">Premium</string>
    <string name="reader_select_chapter_dialog_title">Select a chapter</string>
    <string name="reader_select_page_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="reader_select_page_dialog_select">Choose</string>
    <string name="reader_select_page_dialog_title">Choose a page</string>
    <string name="reader_select_reading_mode_dialog_title">Select reading mode</string>
    <string name="reader_settings_show_guide_key">reader_show_guide</string>
    <string name="reader_settings_speed_key">reader_speed</string>
    <string name="reader_settings_text_size_default_value">20</string>
    <string name="reader_settings_text_size_key">reader_text_size</string>
    <string name="reader_settings_text_size_summary">Select font size</string>
    <string name="reader_settings_text_size_title">Font size</string>
    <string name="reader_speed">Speed %1$d</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_book_ended_change_book">Pick another book</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_book_ended_change_page">Continue</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_book_ended_message">You have read the book to the end</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_book_ended_title">Book is ended</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_completed_message">You have passed the exercise</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_completed_title">Completed</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_end">Finish</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_message">You need to read the text within a specified time period</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_start">Start</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_dialog_title">Timer reading</string>
    <string name="reader_timer_mode_time">Time %1$s</string>
    <string name="reading">Reading</string>
    <string name="reading_3d">3D reading</string>
    <string name="reading_field">Reading field</string>
    <string name="reading_with_a_pencil">Reading with a pencil</string>
    <string name="reading_without_vowels">Reading without vowels</string>
    <string name="recommendation">Recommendations</string>
    <string name="remember_number">Remember the number</string>
    <string name="remember_number_best_score">Best %1$d</string>
    <string name="remember_number_description">"Your task is to remember the displayed number and type it in using keyboard. 

A limited-remainingTime display of numbers accustoms you to the minimum fixation when reading. 

Try to photograph the image of the number in as large fragments as possible, without carefully focusing on individual figures and, if possible, without saying them to yourself. 

This exercise serves to expand the field of view along the horizontal peripheral area. This is a very useful exercise not only for quick reading, but also for other human activities."</string>
    <string name="remember_number_description_title">Remember the number</string>
    <string name="remember_number_result_best_score">Best</string>
    <string name="remember_number_result_new_best">New best</string>
    <string name="remember_number_result_score">Score</string>
    <string name="remember_number_score">Score %1$d</string>
    <string name="remember_words">Remember the words</string>
    <string name="remember_words_description_text">"Fast reading is a set of techniques that help to increase the speed of reading without losing the understanding of what has been read.         

Remember and play the displayed words on the keyboard. This exercise serves to expand the field of view.         

This is a very useful exercise, it will teach you how to memorize text in large fragments and with the maximum understanding of the material you read.         

The trainer will adjust to your level. Limited in duration, the display of words accustoms to the minimum fixation time for reading.         

Be careful to photograph the image of the word as large as possible, without carefully focusing on individual figures and, if possible, do not speak about them yourself.         

Do not waste time learning the technology of fast reading, this in the future will save a lot of time."</string>
    <string name="restart">Restart</string>
    <string name="rules_of_success">Rules of success</string>
    <string name="rules_of_success_title">Recommended for everyday use. By reading the Rules of success regularly, you stimulate yourself to develop the skills which, in your opinion, you lack.</string>
    <string name="s1">Save image</string>
    <string name="s2">Allow Ad to store image in Picture gallery?</string>
    <string name="s3">Accept</string>
    <string name="s4">Decline</string>
    <string name="s5">Create calendar event</string>
    <string name="s6">Allow Ad to create a calendar event?</string>
    <string name="s7">Test Ad</string>
    <string name="schulte_description_image_1_title">Beginner</string>
    <string name="schulte_description_image_2_title">Finding the numbers in 15–20 seconds.</string>
    <string name="schulte_description_image_3_title">Finding the numbers in 8–10 seconds.</string>
    <string name="schulte_description_part_1_message">"Tables with randomly distributed numbers or letters used to check and develop the speed of finding objects in a certain order. 

Exercises with tables allow improving peripheral visual perception, which is important, among other things, for speed reading. 

When you need to invent something, create, write, work with tables, and the process will go to a higher level of concentration, a higher creative level. 

Categories with tables will be useful for almost all types of human activities and at any age."</string>
    <string name="schulte_description_part_1_title">The Schulte table</string>
    <string name="schulte_description_part_2_message">"It is necessary to choose a comfortable place, relax and concentrate on the task. 

The distance from the table to your eyes should be approximately 30–35 cm, the same as when reading a book. 

Before you start, fix your eyes at the grid center and do not move them. All the work is performed with your peripheral vision. 

Find the numbers you need in ascending order from 1 to 25, without omissions and at maximum speed, better without pronouncing the numbers to yourself or aloud. 

It is very important to avoid eye movements away from the center and only look for numbers by peripheral vision. 

The time and frequency of training should be chosen so as to avoid fatigue. 

It is advisable to do this twice a day for 10 minutes. 

As your skill develops, go to 6x6 or 7x7 grid tables."</string>
    <string name="schulte_description_part_2_title">Training mode</string>
    <string name="schulte_description_part_3_message">"Do not try to achieve the maximum result here and now. Everything should go on gradually. Train for three weeks till you reach a certain stable result, then take a break. Go on in a couple of days. 

Gradually, you will see the effect yourself. You will see how your abilities to perceive information, thinking and memory improved. And don’t forget that it’s just a basic exercise for your brain to keep it in good working condition. 

It is impossible to learn speed reading techniques in 3 days. Therefore, adjust yourself to long-term work and receive from reading not only the benefits, but also the pleasure."</string>
    <string name="schulte_description_part_3_title">Conclusion</string>
    <string name="schulte_table">The Schulte table</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_best_time">Best %1$s</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_description_title">The Schulte table</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_next_item">Next %1$s</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_result_best_time">Best</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_result_time">Time</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_column_count_preference_default_value">5</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_column_count_preference_key">schulte_table_column_count</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_column_count_summary">Column count</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_column_count_title">Column count</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_fullscreen_preference_key">schulte_table_fullscreen</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_fullscreen_summary">Schulte table fullscreen mode</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_fullscreen_title">Fullscreen</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_row_count_preference_default_value">5</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_row_count_preference_key">schulte_table_row_count</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_row_count_summary">Row count</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_settings_row_count_title">Row count</string>
    <string name="schulte_table_time">Time %1$s</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">Search</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="share_to_friends">Tell friends</string>
    <string name="sighting_reading">Sighting reading</string>
    <string name="size">Размер</string>
    <string name="special_training">Training</string>
    <string name="special_training_close">Close</string>
    <string name="special_training_message">This exerciser will be presented in the program \"Take the course\" with the achievement of a certain result. During the course, the new exercisers will appear and improve your speed-reading technique. In order not to be torn between all the exercisers at the same time, they were distributed throughout the whole course. This ensures that all the skills necessary for the speed-reading will be well elaborated and brought to automatism.</string>
    <string name="speed">Speed</string>
    <string name="speed_reading">Speed Reading</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_answer_speed_title">Speed</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_author">Yuri Gorbach</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_dialog_answer_no">No thanks</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_dialog_answer_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_dialog_description">Especially for you, we wrote a book that will help you master the speed reading skill much faster. Would you like to read it?</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_dialog_title">Learn all about speed reading</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_language">English</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_name">Speed reading: all secrets</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_purchase_description">Next, you will learn how to get rid of pronunciation in a few days. How to memorize information and store it in long-term memory. How to apply these skills in practice. And much more, very useful information for you.</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_short_first">Speed reading</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_book_short_second">All secrets</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_description_message">"Fix your eyes at the screen center and try to see the whole table. Try to read the table contents with your peripheral vision only, i.e. without moving your eyes. 

Main task is to concentrate on the screen and try to remember the last displayed word, then to press the button with the last remembered word. 

This is a very useful exercise that not only helps you expand your peripheral vision, but also makes you concentrate within a limited show time."</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_description_title">Speed Reading</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_pass_course_result_average_speed">Average speed %1$d</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_pass_course_result_max_speed">Max speed %1$d</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_result_average_speed">Average speed</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_result_best_average_speed">Best</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_result_best_max_speed">Best</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_result_max_speed">Max speed</string>
    <string name="speed_reading_speed">Speed %1$d</string>
    <string name="start_read">Read</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="storm_method">Storm method</string>
    <string name="trainers">Trainers</string>
    <string name="training">Training</string>
    <string name="true_colors">Color confusion</string>
    <string name="true_colors_description_text">The essence of this simulator is as follows: For the shortest period of time, you need to match the screen word and its color, and choose the color in the answer. The perception of color and text occurs in different departments of the hemispheres, the simulator is useful for our brain and it helps to establish new neural connections. Regular work develops the skills of perception and improves concentration of attention. That is extremely important for speed reading.</string>
    <string name="upper_course_short_name">Advanced</string>
    <string name="v7_preference_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="v7_preference_on">ON</string>
    <string name="word_block_result_duration_title">Duration</string>
    <string name="word_block_result_sec">%1$s sec</string>
    <string name="word_block_speed">Speed %1$d</string>
    <string name="word_block_time">Time %1$s</string>
    <string name="word_pairs">Word pairs</string>
    <string name="word_pairs_best_score">Best %1$d</string>
    <string name="word_pairs_description_message">"Find 5 unmatched pairs of words each time the table shows. 

Exercise improves your memory and attention focusing. 

Stay relaxed and choose a convenient option whether to navigate through the columns or rows. This will help you better perceive information and choose words consciously. Try to read silently."</string>
    <string name="word_pairs_description_title">Word pairs</string>
    <string name="word_pairs_result_best_score">Best</string>
    <string name="word_pairs_result_new_best">New best</string>
    <string name="word_pairs_result_score">Score</string>
    <string name="word_pairs_score">Score %1$d</string>
    <string name="words_block">Words Block</string>
    <string name="words_block_word_count">Words %1$d</string>
    <string name="words_columns">Columns of Words</string>
    <string name="year_premium">12 months</string>
</resources>
